>> Brian Holt: 现在让我们来修正该错误， React 不知道这是什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now let's go fix this error
that React doesn't know what this is.
如果你不知道，我们要做的是停止给 Ctrl-C 的服务。
What we're going to do, if you don't know,
to stop the serve you hit Ctrl-C.
我觉得在任何平台上都是有用的
I think that works on any platform.
你向它发送中断命令并说停止这事，对吧 ?
You send an interrupt command to it and
say stop this, right?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我现在会说，现在 npm 安装没有 D ，因为这些
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So here I'm gonna say now
npm install without the D because these
是生产依赖性，反应的反应，就像这样。
are production dependencies,
react react-dom, like that.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这将从 npm 注册表中安装两个软件包。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is gonna go install
our two packages off of the npm registry.
>> Brian Holt: 第二次
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Take a second
去做这个
to do that.
>> Brian Holt: 好，现在不是回我的 index.html，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, now instead
of going back in my index.html,
我要删除这两个剧本文件
I'm gonna delete these two script files.
我不想再把这些装在 CD 上了
Cuz I don't wanna load
these off the CD anymore,
我想把他们从我的电脑上删除
I wanna load them off of my
local computer, so delete that.
所以我们只有 root 和 app.js。
So all we have is the root and our app.js.
>> Brian Holt: 好，现在我们要回到 app.js。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
now we're gonna go back into app.js.
布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我们会在这里说
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we're gonna say up here,
从 "反应" 导入反应。
import React from 'react'.
因此，这将从 React 包中导入缺省导出，好吗 ?
So this is going to import the default
export from the React package, okay?
然后我们会说进口和
And we're going to say import and
我要从反应界说  。
I'm gonna say  from react-dom.
现在，你们中的一些人可能不会在这里看到这个自动完成的情况。
Now, some of you might not be
seeing this autocompletion here.
该扩展称为 NPM Intelisense，它再次在此处。
That extension is called NPM Intellisense,
which again is here.
NPM Intelisense 就在那儿
NPM Intellisense, right there,
>> Brian Holt: 非常有用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Quite useful.
因此，从反应中导入呈现 -DOM 是我们希望从中得到的位置。
So import render from react-DOM is
where we want that one to come from.
>> Brian Holt: 我给你看这个，我可以不用
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I show you this,
I could've just done import without
这里的花括号和反应会像这样
the curly braces here and
said react-DOM like this.
现在这将会起作用，因为这在这里被称为 " rehetDOM " ，但是
And now this would work because this
is called reactDOM down right here, but
我想告诉你怎么输入特定东西
I wanna show you how to
input the specific thing, so
我想从反动 DOM中输入
I wanna import just render from reactDOM.
因此，这表示 reattDOM 具有称为呈示的特定导出，并且
So this is saying reactDOM has
a specific export called render and
我希望你能输入好吗
I want you to input just that, okay?
然后在这里擦掉渲染，就像这样。
And then down here just erase the render,
so it's just render like that.
所以我想说这和破坏是相似的
So I wanna say this is
similar to destructuring.
技术上没有破坏，这就是模块的工作方式。
It's technically not destructuring,
this is just how modules work.
但这只是说 " 反应 " 有一个特定的例子
But this is just saying react-dom
has a specific instance,
导出渲染等于什么， heah，问题?
export render equals something,
heah, question?
>> 演讲者 2: 当您使用 import 语句时，您如何知道是还是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: When you're using an import
statement, how do you know whether or
你不应该用花括号吗
not you should use the curly braces?
是否仅用于导入一个特定功能部件 ?
Is that just for if you want to
import one specific feature?
>> Brian Holt: 是。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yes.
>> 演讲者 2: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
>> Brian Holt: 例如，从 React中
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: For
example here from React,
我其实可以进口具体的东西。
I can actually import specific things.
就像我不能只进口克里德元素
So like, I cannot actually
just import creed element,
因为它是专门出口的对吧
because it specifically exports that,
right?
然后我就不使用了，我只是用这样的创作元素。
And then I wouldn't be using, I would
just be using create element like that.
一般来说，我鼓励你做一些具体的出口。
In general, I would encourage you
to do specific exports most of
因为包裹会为你做点什么
the time because parcel will do
a thing for you called tree shaking.
它实际上是在无视树木颤抖的真实情况
It actually uglifies the actual
thing that does the tree shaking,
但这才是生活密码的包容
but what that does is
it's live code inclusion.
因此，它将只包含可能运行的代码。
So it will only include code
that could ever potentially run.
所以在这个特殊情况下，让我们说 " 反应 " 有 1000 种方法
So in this particular case,
let's say react-dom had 1,000 methods and
我们只进口 1个，对，不包括另外 999个。
we're only importing 1, right,
it would not include the other 999.
如果他们的包装是正确的，如果因为大多数人都不这样做的话。
If they packaged it correctly which is
a big if because most of them don't.
但就像一个像低破折号一样的好例子吗 ?
But like a good example that
would be like low dash right?
低破折号是一个巨大的库，有 200 种方法吗?
Low dash is a huge library
has like 200 methods right?
你没有，从来没有人使用过 200 种方法吗 ?
And you don't,
no one ever uses all 200 methods right?
所以你想做的就是想进口几种方法
So what you wanna do with that is you
wanna import just a few methods that you
然后就不包括其他的了吧
use and then it won't include
the other ones, right?
就像那里的好处
That is like the benefit there,
可能并不总是那样的
potentially, it doesn't
always work out that way.
>> Brian Holt: 对于我，它仅帮助我明确表示我知道这仅使用
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: For me it just helps me to
be explicit that I know this only uses
做出反应的人
render from react-dom.
所以我想说的是这对我毫无帮助
So what I wanted to get to is,
this actually isn't helpful,
因为如果你把你的反应也包括在你的反应中
because if you include react-dom
you get the whole thing,
因为它没有被包装在树上
because it's not packaged for
tree shaking.
然后另一件事就是里面没有太多浪费的东西
And then the other thing is that there's
not a lot of wasteful stuff inside
会有多难的反应所以也不会有太多的树木晃动
react-dom, so there's not a lot
to tree shake out anyway.
所以现在如果我们把这个保存，再回到我们的项目上，它还是应该工作的，对吧 ?
So now if we save this and go back over to
our project, it should still work, right?
现在，你必须运行项目， npm 运行 dev，就像这样。
So now, you have to run the project
of course, npm run dev, like that.
>> Brian Holt: 一旦完成构建，您可以看到此外观类似于 JS
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Once it's finished
building, you can see this looks like a JS
文件正在装入，仅装入此 app.js 文件。
file that's loading,
it's only loading this app.js file.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
it's not loading anything else,
它没有像其他文件那样装载
it's not loading like those
other files from the repo.
因此，你可以看到，这种反应现在被包括在我们的 app.js 中，而不是
So you can see that that reacts now being
included inside of our app.js instead of
正在从其他 CDN 装入。
being loaded from some other CDN.
你可以看到它比这里要大得多
And you can see that it's much
larger than it used to be here,
现在是 965 KB 而不是
now it's 965 KB instead of being,
就像之前的五个一样因为它包括了雷法
like the probably 5 it was before
because it includes React.
现在记住，这是发展环境，意味着它是巨大的。
Now keep in mind this is the development
environment which means it's massive.
如果我把它打成这样产量就会小得多
If I patched this for
production it would be much, much smaller.
因此，在实际执行生产构建之前，不要担心文件大小。
So don't worry about file sizes until
you actually do the production builds,
所以记住这一点
so just keep that in mind.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，这个项目大概是 35 KB，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right now,
this project would probably be 35 KB,
我猜库兹约 32岁了
I guess, cuz React is about 32.